hey guys this is a fun one we want to
find the area of this red region if you
want to try it on your own pause it
right now cuz I'm going to solve it in 3
2 one for the first step let's call this
red region X I'm going to find X by
tackling everything else around it we
have a square right here and another
Square here we have this triangle here
we have this region right here I don't
even know what you would call that and
then we have the same type of region
right here and then right here we have a
thing called a segment of a circle and
then up here we have another segment of
a circle so if we can find the area of
all of these blue pieces then we can add
that to X and set it equal to the whole
Square so first let's do these two
squares the sides of these squares are
equal to four and the area of a square
is equal to the side length squared so
we'll plug in four for the side length
and four squar is equal to 16 so both of
these have an area of 16 and now that
we've solved these let's make them
orange and let's put them back and next
let's look at this triangle both of
these sides are equal to four and the
area of a triangle is base * height / 2
we can plug in four for the base and
four